N-No way...
He's...
I redirected the shockwaves
into the ground.
But you really startled me
with that move!
I honestly had no clue
the Righteous Egg
held this much power.
His aura is much more powerful
and larger than the last Devils'...
I was a fool.
I never had a chance.
Father, I'm so sorry.
I wasn't good enough, after all.
Most Devils have two horns...
Do you know why I have three?
A Devil's horns are
a sign of their power.
The more horns they have,
the more powerful they are.
The White Demon...
So, do you get it now?
You picked the wrong fight.
That's enough!
Don't be so impatient.
I'll kill you nice and slow, later.
Miss Elizabeth...
How does it feel?
To die without saving your father?
Well, it's a meaningless bond,
I guess.
Maybe it isn't worth fretting over.
You can die now.
Is this it?
K-Keiji?
B-Brother...
What are you trying to pull
at this point?
I'm not done with you yet!
EPISODE 11
IT TAKES TWO WINGS TO FLY
I feel so lonely.
I wonder when Father will return?
Hey, Keisuke...
I hear your old man has another
new girlfriend!
- Liar!
- Your dad's a man whore
- Cheater!
- Man whore!
What did you say?!
Don't disrespect my father!
Now you've done it!
- Stay down, ya wimp.
- Don't mess with us!
Father...
Help me! Father!
Cut it out, you guys!
Kasumi!
Stop it!
You're hurting Keisuke!
Kasumi, the girl I l-l-love,
is defending me?!
Shut up!
Beat her up too!
Tough talk coming from a girl...
- Idiot!
- Stop it! Help!
Keisuke, help me!
I'm so sorry, Kasumi...
...is what my Mom said!
- That's hilarious.
- Right?
Um...
Th-Thank you for standing up
for me yesterday.
- Let's go.
- Yup, let's go.
What was I supposed to do?
Anybody would run
in that situation.
It's not my fault.
Keisuke.
Have you been a good kid?
F-Father!
When did you get home?
Just now.
Keisuke, I have something important
to talk to you about.
W-What?
Y-You want me to fight Demons?
Why me?
You're joking, right?
I'm serious.
It's time for you to fulfill
the Goshikidori Family's destiny.
Starting today, I will teach you
the Path of the Heavenly Fist.
This is so sudden...
I can't do something like that!
What's a Goshikidori?
What are you talking about?
It's a Demon, Keisuke!
Come with me!
W-What?!
Let me sing!!
Listen to me hum a tune!!
A-Amazing...
He beat that giant monster
so easily...
Father...
Can I become as strong
as you one day?
Yes. You have the same blood
flowing through your veins!
I have to give it my all.
I'm going to become a cool warrior
just like Father!
15, 16, 17...
21, 22...
You're wide open!
Father, do I have the talent
to be a warrior?
Keisuke, do you know
what true strength is?
I-I don't...
It's the one thing that you have
to find yourself, Keisuke.
Until then, you must train.
I trained like hell...
But never found the answer...
Was my strength all just for show?
To be honest...
Wanting to save the world
was just a front...
I just wanted to be like Father...
Nothing's changed since that day...
It's a miracle I even got this far,
for being so worthless...
I did everything that I could.
I have no regrets
Big Brother...
What are you doing?
You're weaker than I am.
You don't stand a chance!
Just stop now...
Are you crazy?
What can you do in that condition?
What else is there to do?
I'm going to kick your ass.
Keiji, stop!!
You're going to die
if you keep going!
Listen to me, Hikari.
You must not kill that one.
Instead, try pushing him
right to the brink of death.
I want to test a theory.
Why is she so interested in him?
Keiji!
Mo...
Morio!
Keiji! I've wanted to see you!
How have you been?!
Morio... you're killing me...
Oh! S-Sorry!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Where's Piyoko?
Over there.
She risked her life to defeat
the monster in my head.
I owe her my life.
Not bad, Piyoko!
Keiji, I heard what you did.
How you came to save me.
You're such a good guy!
I just happened to be passing by.
What?!
Is that right?
Either way, I'm happy!
What's up with this conversation?!
Even so...
I'm very angry at that guy.
Controlling us Demons...
Making us destroy towns...
Making trouble for
Keiji and his friends...
My heart hurt all that time.
I'm never... letting you...
...get away with this!
Morio!
Know your place, trash.
You bastard!!
Something's off.
Why isn't he finishing us off?
Is he toying with us?
Keiji... please stop already!
You've done enough, Big Brother...
You fought well.
But it's no use...
We totally lost...
Keiji...
Sorry, but I'm a stubborn bird.
Stop!
How does he still
have the strength?
H-How?
You're weaker than I am,
but how can you still fight?
He doesn't stand a chance...
Why isn't his spirit broken?!
Keisuke!
Do you know what true strength is?
Father, I understand now.
Ever since I was young,
I blamed others for my problems.
I made excuses and
ran from my problems.
My heart is just so weak!
I never wanted to admit it.
I didn't want to acknowledge
my own weakness.
Big Brother...
You're strong...
He overcame his painful past.
He doesn't cower in fear.
He believes in himself,
and lives on his own terms!
To be honest...
I've always wanted to be...
a man like you, Big Brother!
What is this?
Power is growing deep inside of me.
Could it be?
Through your training,
your Righteous Egg should
be powerful enough
to undergo a second awakening.
If you do so,
you can unlock a new power.
The rest is up to your heart.
My heart?!
Discover the meaning of
true strength, Keisuke.
Playtime is over.
In the end, nothing happened...
I'll let you live for now.
I was able to reach
Second Awakening
thanks to you, Brother.
Thank you.
Leave the rest to me.
The meaning of true strength is...
The strength to believe
in yourself to the end!
I'll no longer...
...give up!
What was that?
That attack came out of nowhere!
Mama... this is getting interesting!
W-What just happened?
It's like he transformed
into someone else!
Keisuke... are you?
Miss Elizabeth,
may I ask you a favor?
Will you use this chance
to find my father?
He's probably being held
inside the factory.
But...!
Please leave this to me.
I will defeat him.
Understood.
I know you can do it.
Thank you.
Keiji.
Don't you dare die on me.
Please beat him!
Got it!
This time around...
I'll protect everyone!
Here he comes!
I can see it!
Amazing...
So, this is the Righteous Egg's
Second Awakening.
Why you...
There's no escape!
That's it!
Hiding in the rubble...
...Goshikidori?!
Where is he?
Fifth Fist Heavenly Path!
Ultra-Explosive Chicken Leg!
I won...
What changed you?
My brother awakened
my inner strength.
I see...
So, you were siblings.
Also...
I have to save my father.
My father is my inspiration.
I see...
So I was
defeated by family bonds...
...a true bond.
Bonds...
Hikari...
Hikari... my precious Hikari...
Who... is that?
What?!
Sorry about that, Mama...
I got caught off guard, myself...
Not here either...
Where is Keisuke's father?!
- There he is!
- Oops.
Wait!
What's the matter, fly up
and get him, dumb chicken!
Who are you calling dumb?
Hi, Sophia?
Activate "Jet" please.
Roger.
Hold it!
What?! Damn it!
Let that rooster go!
Why would I do that, dummy?!
Call me a dummy again!
Damn it!
She's closing in!
From the looks of it,
that was a Kappa Demon.
So, if we fight underwater,
I'll be at a disadvantage.
Looks like she isn't coming in.
Guess it's a war of attrition.
Screw my orders.
Not my problem if this one dies.
Ow!
Looks like I was passed out.
Is that...
How long will you keep running,
Goshikidori!
Both his speed and power
have increased significantly.
He can regenerate,
there's no point in
attacking him relentlessly.
I need to target his vitals.
Playtime is over.
Take this!
You fell for it!
Now this is what I call a birdcage!
Damn it! It's so dark,
I can't see anything!
Welcome to hell!
Savor it.
It's no use trying to see.
I need to feel it.
Listen...
Feel how the air is moving!
I got it!
It's so clear!
I see, the Second Awakening has
made my senses sharper!
Why can't I hit him?!
I can do this!
What?!
Damnー!
Ultra Explosive Chicken Leg!
What?!
His head wasn't his weak spot?!
That'sー!
He's regenerating from that orb!
I don't wanna!
I don't wanna fight!
Please, it hurts!
Mama...
Hikari...
You must fight.
Of course, Mama.
A brutal death will be
my gift to them!
Die, die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die, die!
He's going completely berserk!
He's become totally erratic
and unpredictable!
Keisuke...
Die, die, die, die, die, die!
Morio!
I still got a grudge against you.
You're still alive, you half-wit?
Evil folks like you
can't be left alive.
Wait... Don't... Morio!
Get crushed!
Why you...
Morio!
Even if I die, I won't let go!
K-Keiji...
I'm sorry... I couldn't be useful...
Bye-bye.
Stop!!
M-Morio...
How unfortunate, just when
he had regained his senses.
But his life didn't mean anything, anyway.
He was just trash, right?
I was born a fluke.
I had a reason to live, after all!
Bastard... How dare you...
do that to Morio...
Brother... could that beー?!
What is that?
What are you doing?
Finally,
his Righteous Egg is...
Mark my words, you bastard!
I will end you!
Is it all over?
We haven't settled it, Brother!
That's right, Keiji!
Don't let your guard down!
It's all about duty, Mister!
Next time: "What the Birds,
Beasts and Trees Share."
Each and every last one of them
makes my crown curl!
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS